https://www.eaglestalent.com/privacy-policy/

SpeakersAboutAboutOur TeamClientsTestimonialsResourcesFAQVirtualTypes of EventsPopular Speakers and TopicsBenefits of VirtualVirtual: Live or Pre-RecordedGo Virtual: Your Backup PlanVirtual Event TipsTop Engaging Virtual PromosVirtual TestimonialsContact UsContact UsSpeaker SubmissionCareersBlogPortalMy Speakers
1-973-313-9800
Search Name/Keyword
SELECT TOPICBusiness SpeakersCEO SpeakersHuman Resources SpeakersTaxesCorporate Culture SpeakersGenerational DiversityDiversity and InclusionTime ManagementBranding & AdvertisingSocial Media SpeakersStrategic PlanningSales StrategiesWorkplace Safety SpeakersRetailRecruitment & RetentionReal Estate SpeakersPeak PerformanceOrganizational SkillsNetworking SpeakersNegotiationMarketing SpeakersManagement SpeakersFinance & InsuranceFuturist SpeakersEthics & ValuesBusiness EntrepreneurshipEconomics SpeakersCustomer ServiceCorporate Social ResponsibilitySustainability SpeakersAlliances & PartnershipsGlobal Business SolutionsBusiness GrowthWomen In Business SpeakersConsumer BehaviorSmall Business DevelopmentModerator/Q&ASocial Entrepreneur & CausesBig DataCyber Security & Identity TheftMillennials in the WorkforceBrand PowerDisruptionInnovation SpeakersCreativity SpeakersArtificial Intelligence (AI) SpeakersRobotics SpeakersVirtual Keynote SpeakersCelebrityReality TV StarsCelebrity Chef SpeakersCollege & EducationLGBTQ SpeakersAddictionCampus & UniversityGraduation and CommencementCulture & ArtsTED ConferenceHome & GardenPhotographersMedia PersonalitiesFood & Wine/ HospitalityArts & Pop CultureDinner EventsHispanic/ LatinoChinaActivismEntertainmentArt PerformancesEntertainment with a MessageHosts & EmceesMentalists & HypnotistsJugglersMagicians/ IllusionistsVentriloquistsPolitical HumorImpersonatorsComedy SpeakersRevues & Variety ShowsMusicians & SingersCirque Shows/ AcrobatsComedy HeadlinersTribute BandsParty/ Dance BandsSinging ImpressionistsEntertainersHealthcareNutritionCancer AwarenessDisability IssuesStress ManagementHealthcare SpeakersHealth & WellnessAgingPatient SafetyCOVID-19 SpeakersMotivational SpeakersAccountability SpeakersMountain ClimbersInspirational SpeakersLife Balance SpeakersTeam Building SpeakersEmpowerment SpeakersMotivationalLeadership SpeakersHumorist SpeakersGoal SettingChange SpeakersOvercoming AdversityAchievementSuccess SpeakersStorytellingWomen EmpowermentWomen In Leadership SpeakersChristian SpeakersInteractive SpeakersPersonal DevelopmentParentingYouth IssuesReligion & SpiritualityWomen's IssuesSpouse ProgramsRelationshipsPresentation SkillsEducation SpeakersCommunication SpeakersEmotional IntelligenceScience & TechnologyScienceTechnology SpeakersAstronautsSTEM SpeakersSports SpeakersWinter SportsFitnessGymnasticsHockey/ NHLNFL SpeakersCoaches & ManagersAuto RacingBasketball/ NBASwimmingOlympiansBaseball/ MLBSports AnnouncersAdventurersSports StarsWomen In SportsTrending TopicsHot Motivational SpeakersHot Happiness SpeakersHot Business SpeakersTrending HealthcareHot Sports SpeakersHot Celebrity SpeakersTrending Fresh Perspective KeynotesGranted to Attract Diverse Markets
SELECT TOPIC
XBusiness SpeakersArtificial Intelligence (AI) SpeakersAlliances & PartnershipsBig DataBrand PowerBranding & AdvertisingBusiness EntrepreneurshipBusiness GrowthCEO SpeakersConsumer BehaviorCorporate Culture SpeakersCorporate Social ResponsibilityCreativity SpeakersCustomer ServiceCyber Security & Identity TheftDisruptionDiversity and InclusionEconomics SpeakersEthics & ValuesFinance & InsuranceFuturist SpeakersGenerational DiversityGlobal Business SolutionsHuman Resources SpeakersInnovation SpeakersManagement SpeakersMarketing SpeakersMillennials in the WorkforceModerator/Q&ANegotiationNetworking SpeakersOrganizational SkillsPeak PerformanceReal Estate SpeakersRecruitment & RetentionRetailRobotics SpeakersSales StrategiesSmall Business DevelopmentSocial Entrepreneur & CausesSocial Media SpeakersStrategic PlanningSustainability SpeakersTaxesTime ManagementVirtual Keynote SpeakersWomen In Business SpeakersWorkplace Safety SpeakersCelebrityCelebrity Chef SpeakersReality TV StarsCollege & EducationAddictionCampus & UniversityGraduation and CommencementLGBTQ SpeakersCulture & ArtsActivismArts & Pop CultureChinaDinner EventsFood & Wine/ HospitalityHispanic/ LatinoHome & GardenMedia PersonalitiesPhotographersTED ConferenceEntertainmentArt PerformancesCirque Shows/ AcrobatsComedy HeadlinersComedy SpeakersEntertainersEntertainment with a MessageHosts & EmceesImpersonatorsJugglersMagicians/ IllusionistsMentalists & HypnotistsMusicians & SingersParty/ Dance BandsPolitical HumorRevues & Variety ShowsSinging ImpressionistsTribute BandsVentriloquistsHealthcareAgingCancer AwarenessCOVID-19 SpeakersDisability IssuesHealth & WellnessHealthcare SpeakersNutritionPatient SafetyStress ManagementMotivational SpeakersAccountability SpeakersAchievementChange SpeakersChristian SpeakersEmpowerment SpeakersGoal SettingHumorist SpeakersInspirational SpeakersInteractive SpeakersLeadership SpeakersLife Balance SpeakersMotivationalMountain ClimbersOvercoming AdversityStorytellingSuccess SpeakersTeam Building SpeakersWomen EmpowermentWomen In Leadership SpeakersPersonal DevelopmentCommunication SpeakersEducation SpeakersEmotional IntelligenceParentingPresentation SkillsRelationshipsReligion & SpiritualitySpouse ProgramsWomen's IssuesYouth IssuesScience & TechnologyAstronautsScienceSTEM SpeakersTechnology SpeakersSports SpeakersAdventurersAuto RacingBaseball/ MLBBasketball/ NBACoaches & ManagersFitnessGymnasticsHockey/ NHLNFL SpeakersOlympiansSports AnnouncersSports StarsSwimmingWinter SportsWomen In SportsTrending TopicsHot Business SpeakersHot Celebrity SpeakersHot Happiness SpeakersHot Motivational SpeakersHot Sports SpeakersTrending Fresh Perspective KeynotesTrending HealthcareGranted to Attract Diverse Markets
IN-PERSON FEE RANGE$2,500 - $5,000$5,001 - $7,500$7,501 - $10,000$10,001 - $15,000$15,001 - $20,000$20,001 - $30,000$30,001 - $50,000$50,001+
IN-PERSON FEE RANGE
X$2,500 - $5,000$5,001 - $7,500$7,501 - $10,000$10,001 - $15,000$15,001 - $20,000$20,001 - $30,000$30,001 - $50,000$50,001+
SPEAKER'S LOCATIONAlabamaAlaskaArizonaArkansasCaliforniaColoradoConnecticutDelawareDistrict of ColumbiaFloridaGeorgiaHawaiiIdahoIllinoisIndianaIowaKansasKentuckyLousianaMaineMarylandMassachusettsMichiganMinnesotaMississippiMissouriMontanaNebraskaNevadaNew HampshireNew JerseyNew MexicoNew YorkNorth CarolinaNorth DakotaOhioOklahomaOregonPennsylvaniaRhode IslandSouth CarolinaSouth DakotaTennesseeTexasUtahVermontVirginiaWashingtonWest VirginiaWisconsinWyomingAlberta, CanadaOntario, CanadaN/ABritish Columbia, CanadaCanadaLondonEnglandQuebec, CanadaNova Scotia, CanadaNew Brunswick, CanadaManitoba, CanadaPrince Edward Island, CanadaSaskatchewan, CanadaNewfoundland and Labrador, CanadaPuerto RicoCosta RicaSingaporeAustralia
SPEAKER LOCATION
XAlabamaAlaskaArizonaArkansasCaliforniaColoradoConnecticutDelawareDistrict of ColumbiaFloridaGeorgiaHawaiiIdahoIllinoisIndianaIowaKansasKentuckyLousianaMaineMarylandMassachusettsMichiganMinnesotaMississippiMissouriMontanaNebraskaNevadaNew HampshireNew JerseyNew MexicoNew YorkNorth CarolinaNorth DakotaOhioOklahomaOregonPennsylvaniaRhode IslandSouth CarolinaSouth DakotaTennesseeTexasUtahVermontVirginiaWashingtonWest VirginiaWisconsinWyomingAlberta, CanadaOntario, CanadaN/ABritish Columbia, CanadaCanadaLondonEnglandQuebec, CanadaNova Scotia, CanadaNew Brunswick, CanadaManitoba, CanadaPrince Edward Island, CanadaSaskatchewan, CanadaNewfoundland and Labrador, CanadaPuerto RicoCosta RicaSingaporeAustralia
SELECT PROGRAM TYPEInteractive ExperienceVirtual Meeting/ConferenceKeynote SpeakingBreakout Session or WorkshopExpert PanelFull DayHalf DayModerator for Q & A or EmceeEntertainment for OrganizationsAfter-DinnerPerformance for General AudienceLecture Series / Sit Down Q & A
SELECT PROGRAM
XInteractive ExperienceVirtual Meeting/ConferenceKeynote SpeakingBreakout Session or WorkshopExpert PanelFull DayHalf DayModerator for Q & A or EmceeEntertainment for OrganizationsAfter-DinnerPerformance for General AudienceLecture Series / Sit Down Q & A
Clear ResultsPrivacy PolicyWho we areOur website address is: https://www.eaglestalent.com.What personal data we collect and why we collect itCommentsWhen visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.MediaIf you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.Contact formsCookiesIf you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.If you visit our login page, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.Embedded content from other websitesArticles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracking your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.AnalyticsWho we share your data withHow long we retain your dataIf you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.What rights you have over your dataIf you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.Where we send your dataVisitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.
Eagles Talent
57 West South Orange Avenue
South Orange,
NJ
07079Phone: 1-973-313-9800Phone: 1-973-313-9800Email for general inquiries:info@eaglestalent.comSpeakersAboutResourcesContact UsBlogPortalNewsletterIs your organization looking for trending and proven keynote speakers? Sign up here to receive monthly suggestions from our team.
By continuing to browse, you consent to our use of cookies. To know more, please view our Privacy Policy.
Hide
